https://hvsglobal.co.uk/privacy-policy

Add to Cart
Waterlogic PU-4076 Taste & Odour Reduction Filter & Scale Inhibitor
Privacy Policy
HVS Global regards the lawful and correct treatment of personal information important to maintaining confidence between those with whom we deal and ourselves. HVS Global treats personal information lawfully and correctly. To this end HVS Global fully endorses and adheres to the principles of data protection, as set out in the Data Protection Act 1998. Specifically, the personal information:
- shall be processed fairly and lawfully
- shall be obtained only for one or more specified and lawful purposes
- shall be adequate, relevant and not excessive
- shall be accurate and, where necessary, kept up to date;
- shall not be kept longer than is necessary
- shall be processed in accordance with the rights of data subjects under the Act
- shall be kept secure
- not transferred to countries without adequate protection
Personal data is only collected through the HVS Global website for the purpose of processing orders and answering queries. HVS Global website does not store or capture personal information, but merely logs the user's IP address (Internet Protocol: standard allowing data to be transmitted between two devices) which is automatically recognised by the webserver HVS Global website uses cookies for collecting user information from the site and does not collect any information about you except that required for system administration of the website. Further information regarding the Data Protection Act can be found on the Government's website.
Continue
Latest Products
Borg & Overstrom Foot Switch Dispenser
£72.59
Add to Cart
Add to Wish List
Add to Compare
HVS Water Cooler Starter Kit
